hemsmail.com 2017-11-29

# Privacy Policy - Email Marketing India | SMTP Server India - Email Marketing India | SMTP Server India - HemsMail

### PRIVACY STATEMENT

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.hemsmail.com

### HEMSTM MAIL HAS AGREED TO NOTIFY YOU OF:

  * What personally identifiable information of yours or third party’s is collected from you through the web site
  * The organization that is collecting the information
  * How the information is used
  * With whom the information may be shared
  * What are the choices available to you with regards to collection, use and distribution of the information
  * What are the kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information that is under HemsTM Mail’s control
  * How can you correct any inaccuracies in the information collected

### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

Any information collected on this site becomes the property of HemsTM Mail. HemsTM Mail will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any way which is different from what is disclosed in this statement. We collect information from our users at several different points on our website.

### INFORMATION YOU UPLOAD INTO HEMSTM MAIL

HemsTM Mail offers self-service email based direct marketing solutions for small and mid-size businesses. The client data which is uploaded into our system is stored in a secure location. HemsTM Mail does not sell or rent any client data that has been loaded on to our system. Only the registered account holder can gain access to the uploaded lists.

### REGISTRATION

No registration is required to view the HemsTM Mail website.

### LOG FILES

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### SHARING

We will share average or approximate demographic information with 3rd parties in the case they would like to know demographics of our audience. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We do not share personally identifiable information with 3rd parties.

### LINKS

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we at HemsTM Mail are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by hemsmail.com.

### SECURITY

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.  
All HemsTM Mail’s servers are protected by firewalls. We also take stringent measures to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information is restricted access only. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. All our employees use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to protected information. Furthermore, ALL employees are updated as to our security and privacy practices. Every month, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers’ information is protected. Finally, the physical servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure collocation facility, within locked cages that only HemsTMMail network administrators have access to. This facility provides security 24 hours a day, 365 days a year and guaranties our servers against power outages by using automated backup power systems.

### SPECIAL OFFERS

We send all new members a verification email to verify password and user name. Established members who have chosen it receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

### ADMINISTRATIVE TYPE EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS

You will receive administrative emails that are related to the usage of our service. You may not opt-out of administrative emails. These administrative emails do not have any marketing, promotional or advertising material(s) in them.

### CORRECTION/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION

If your personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if you no longer desire our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update that personal data provided to us. You can do this can be done by calling on telephone number at 0141-2657805 or by sending us an email to our Customer Support at support@HemsTMMail.in. If you want your account deactivated please state this in your communications and we will do this.

### NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will prominently post those changes on our Homepage (located at http://www.hemsmail.com) so our users know what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any time we need to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

### LEGAL DISCLAIMER

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our Web site.

### UNSOLICITED EMAIL MESSAGES

Policy against advertising our website using unsolicited email messages We require that all e-mails promoting Hems Mail or its services are sent only to clients who have agreed to receive such messages. We prohibit any advertising of our brand and Web site using unsolicited email messages. Not complying with this policy will cause partnership termination and/or affiliate account termination.

If you feel you’ve been sent unsolicited emails promoting our brand or website and would like to register a complaint, please email our abuse department at: abuse@hemsmail.com. We will immediately investigate all allegations made related to unsolicited messages.

Or write us at:  
313, Rajpark Gali No. 6

Jaipur, Rajasthan, India-302004
